Who are you?
Mr. Konta invited us over!
Isn't this just like…
Our very own reality dating show?
I have a members-only service
where I post all about entrepreneurship.
Would you like to subscribe to my service?
I really don't want to get a sunburn.
Could we swap seats?
Actually, should we just head inside?
A Pinot Noir from Burgundy?
If you decant it a bit more,
the aroma will open up.
They sound smart when they talk,
but they feel weirdly shallow.
They are completely empty inside.
Will Mr. Konta be back soon?
We came here
because we wanted to talk to him!
Mr. Konta, the millionaire
who got to retire at a young age.
Say what?
TWO HOURS EARLIER
Radish? One hundred yen?
These…
These are turnips. Red turnips.
Tatsumi Town feels much cooler
compared to Tokyo.
It seems inbound tourism
is driving up foreign demand around here,
making it the next big business spot!
A mentor at a seminar told me.
Seems like more Japanese business owners
are setting up villas here lately, too.
We need to expand our network
of wealthy contacts here
to outmaneuver the other young startups.
Though, at first glance,
there doesn't seem to be
anyone wealthy around here.
Idiot.
Real millionaires, they wear Uniqlo,
drive a Vitz,
and spend their weekends
eating at their villas.
Ordinary people just see them as ordinary.
But we're different, right?
As fellow business professionals,
we have to spot
the hidden aura within them.
But listen, like, today,
these tiny little turnips
were ridiculously cheap!
Radi? Radi…
Whatever, they're turnips!
They were practically giving them away!
So, I bought the entire stock!
Every single one! See ya later.
-He said "stock."
-What? She hung up already?
-Man, Midori…
-Go talk to him!
You go!
Excuse me.
Can we talk for a moment?
I knew the second I saw you
at the roadside station, Mr. Konta!
I knew you were someone extraordinary!
Well, you know,
I do appear on TV a fair bit,
so yes, I guess.
So?
What made you so interested in me?
My young friends.
Did my aura give me away?
I guess I just couldn't hide it?
Yes! You have an aura!
Please teach us the secret
to your success, Mr. Konta.
How you became a millionaire
at a young age!
What?
"Okuribito"?
Oh, that movie that won the Oscar?
I wasn't in Departures!
I didn't star in it!
He's misunderstanding that?
They weren't talking about the movie.
Konta is too stupid.
But seriously, this villa is incredible!
After coming here, we know this
is exactly the lifestyle we're aiming for!
Well, look at you guys. So passionate.
Are you all in the industry too?
Yes! We're still
just starting out, though.
You should have said so earlier!
I'll listen to whatever you want to share.
Then to start off,
what would you say
was your core strength in business?
Well, let's see…
I would say business is like…
taming tigers.
What?
You were on Business Tigers?
BUSINESS TIGERS
I'm betting the full amount.
He didn't mean that show!
Wait, what did he mean?
Konta was talking about
wrangling extras on set.
But lately, you know,
I'm not really in that phase anymore.
Incredible.
Miraculously,
their conversations match up.
We need to clear up
their misunderstanding fast.
They're all idiots, so they synced up.
Hey, Rinrin.
Could you go tell them that my brother
is just an unsuccessful actor?
I've already lost interest
in those three morons.
You're already on a dating app!
Do we have more guests?
My brother dragged three people here.
Oh!
Turnips!
So Konta was talking about radishes!
Guess I'll make a salad.
You should have some too.
We're doing a barbecue today!
No, I…
Oh, come on. Please stay and eat.
Okay.
Mr. Konta.
The three of us
actually post videos online.
Would you consider appearing in one?
I'm sure tons of young people
want to hear your story!
Of course!
But make sure to film me from this angle.
This side of my face looks sharper.
Here, look.
I see it.
They post videos? What kind of videos?
They sent me the link
when we were talking earlier.
They have 62 subscribers.
That's so few.
"The Three Growth Musketeers.
To aim for FIRE, you must take risks now!"
It's one of those seminar-style channels!
And so today, we asked Gen Z success story
Mr. Konta all about his work-life balance,
here at his villa!
See you in the next video!
Buh-bye!
Thank you so much!
-Thank you very much!
-How were my looks?
You were top-tier!
My look is on point today!
I'm totally serving!
Mr. Nishigami, you chopped the firewood?
Thank you!
-You were on form!
-I'm going to burn lots.
-Thank you.
-Konta!
-Yes.
-We're about to start!
Okay.
Oh, right. You should join us.
Wait, may we?
Thank you so much!
Truly a winner at life!
Come on, you three.
Come on! Look at you, Tetsuro.
You're working super hard.
Seats.
Well then, here's to new encounters.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
Thank you.
Welcome.
Is this pork?
It's not beef.
My drink is all gone.
Huh? Is there any sauce? Sauce.
Hey, pitch in and help! What's with them?
They're just sitting around!
They really don't think at all.
They are empty boys.
Why did I even want
these three to like me?
Here! Start grilling your own food!
Thank you.
Let's grill it.
Should we?
Watch out.
Are you members of any online communities?
Huh? Online communities?
No, we aren't in any.
Then how do you build your networks?
Never mind that, look at your chest.
There's a bug.
Oh, no! No, get it off!
-Calm down.
-What is this?
-It's just a drone beetle.
-Gross!
Gross!
-You're cute.
-A cockroach, so gross.
Go on back to the forest.
No! The meat!
-Oh, crap…
-It's fine. I'll do it. Give.
It's hot.
So hot!
So hot.
You all right?
Can't handle bugs.
Can't grill meat.
What is up with these guys?
Right?
They only came here to network.
Mr. Konta.
I am so, so glad I got to meet you today!
Same. I always want to support
young people working hard.
So, you can ask me for advice anytime.
I actually want to ask you
something right away.
Oh, that really is right away.
-What is it?
-Mr. Konta.
Would you be willing to invest in us?
-Invest?
-Yes!
-Me?
How much?
10,000 yen?
No.
1,000.
Oh, what?
"Invest"? What an exaggeration!
Sure.
Wait.
Really?
Incredible.
I used to borrow money
from my seniors all the time.
Make sure you pay me back.
What?
No.
Not one of these.
Not one?
What we mean
is an investment in our business.
Ten thousand of these.
Say what?
That's ten million yen!
Are you out of your mind?
What are you saying?
I'm an actor.
No way I have that kind of money!
My savings are under 100,000.
Wait.
You're an actor?
Give it back.
Don't look at my 1,000 yen.
Hey, look at this.
SOUSAIDOU ACTORS OFFICE
This guy is an actor.
So that means…
But you were talking stocks.
Stocks?
Oh! I got a nice stock of turnips!
Did you not have the salad?
What?
So by stock, you meant these?
Apparently, they're called radishes.
Or Raditz.
Like Goku's older brother.
I see.
It seems there was a misunderstanding.
So Mr. Konta, you aren't rich?
Of course not!
This is the worst.
I'm covered in bug bites everywhere.
It's the worst.
Jeez, so many bugs!
The meat!
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
What?
-Oh, man!
-That was close!
Can we salvage this?
You should have hedged the risk.
Just go home already! You total airheads!
From now on, you guys better
call yourselves "The Empty Boys"!
"The Empty Boys"?
It's fine.
An empty head just means
you can stuff more dreams into it!
Well then…
Thanks for the food.
Clean up after yourselves!
Don't come back!
Oh, there are tons of bugs
on the way out. So here.
-Thank you.
-You can have it.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
-Bye. See you again.
-We'll come again.
Thank you!
Still, I don't think I have any right
to look down on those guys.
What?
I think I might be empty too.
When it comes to work and romance.
And intelligence?
But today, I think I finally figured out
who I should really be looking at.
What's with you?
Konta.
Let me help you!
Oh, Rinrin, thanks.
Watch out for the ash.
-Got it.
-All right.
Mr. Nishigami!
Thank you for earlier.
It was nothing.
Well…
I am really grateful.
Mr. Nishigami…
You protected me from the fire.
Well…
I…
Please excuse me.
Mr. Nishigami!
See you tomorrow!
Look at this.
Oh, the video from the other day?
They actually uploaded it.
COMMENTS
-What?
-What's with these comments?
Huh? Why is everyone talking about stocks?
Because they're all idiots.
Hey, look at the channel name.
"The Empty Boys: We're Gonna Smash It!"
Huh? I don't get it.
Well, they weren't dating material,
but maybe they're decent guys?
Nope. Not at all!
So harsh. Brutal.
WE SPOKE TO SUCCESSFUL BUSINESSMAN
KONTA HOSHINO!
-Isn't this hilarious?
-Yeah.
I stumbled on it while looking
at a channel run by my college friends!
This guy isn't bad…
You know, he might actually
be pretty interesting.
On me?
Did something happen to Konta?
I bet he failed another audition.
Do you know a show called
Document Memoreal?
They want to do a feature on me.
Say what?
-Let me carry that.
-Mr. Nishigami.
I'm happy for Mr. Konta.
Good morning.
I'm Torihara from Document Memoreal.
Why those outfits and makeup?
We might be on camera too.
I look forward to working with you all!
-He's getting carried away.
-Is he really going to be okay?
He thinks he'll go viral
and become popular.
You're being tricked.
I'm the actor, Konta Hoshino.
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.